#using 3 dictionaries to store the possible questions and answers

level_1 = {
    "question1": {
        "question" : "This is question 1",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 1",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 1",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 1",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 1",
        }
    },
    "question2": {
        "question" : "This is question 2",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 2",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 2",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 2",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 2",
        }
    },
    "question3": {
        "question" : "This is question 3",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 3",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 3",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 3",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 3",
        }
    },
    "question4": {
        "question" : "This is question 4",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 4",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 4",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 4",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 4",
        }
    },
    "question5": {
        "question" : "This is question 5",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 5",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 5",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 5",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 5",
        }
    },
    "question6": {
        "question" : "This is question 6",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 6",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 6",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 6",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 6",
        }
    },
    "question7": {
        "question" : "This is question 7",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 7",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 7",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 7",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 7",
        }
    },
    "question8": {
        "question" : "This is question 8",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 8",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 8",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 8",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 8",
        }
    },
    "question9": {
        "question" : "This is question 9",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 9",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 9",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 9",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 9",
        }
    },
    "question10": {
        "question" : "This is question 10",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 10",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 10",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 10",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 10",
        }
    },
}  

#level 2 questions
level_2 = {
    "question11": {
        "question" : "This is question 11",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 11",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 11",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 11",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 11",
        }
    },
    "question12": {
        "question" : "This is question 12",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 12",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 12",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 12",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 12",
        }
    },
    "question13": {
        "question" : "This is question 13",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 13",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 13",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 13",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 13",
        }
    },
    "question14": {
        "question" : "This is question 14",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 14",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 14",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 14",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 14",
        }
    },
    "question15": {
        "question" : "This is question 15",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 15",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 15",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 15",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 15",
        }
    },
    "question16": {
        "question" : "This is question 16",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 16",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 16",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 16",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 16",
        }
    },
    "question17": {
        "question" : "This is question 17",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 17",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 17",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 17",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 17",
        }
    },
    "question18": {
        "question" : "This is question 18",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 18",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 18",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 18",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 18",
        }
    },
    "question19": {
        "question" : "This is question 19",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 19",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 19",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 19",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 19",
        }
    },
    "question20": {
        "question" : "This is question 20",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 20",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 20",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 20",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 20",
        }
    },
}


#level 3 questions
level_3 = {
    "question21": {
        "question" : "This is question 21",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 21",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 21",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 21",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 21",
        }
    },
    "question22": {
        "question" : "This is question 22",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 22",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 22",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 22",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 22",
        }
    },
    "question23": {
        "question" : "This is question 23",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 23",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 23",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 23",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 23",
        }
    },
    "question24": {
        "question" : "This is question 24",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 24",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 24",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 24",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 24",
        }
    },
    "question25": {
        "question" : "This is question 25",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 25",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 25",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 25",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 25",
        }
    },
    "question26": {
        "question" : "This is question 26",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 26",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 26",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 26",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 26",
        }
    },
    "question27": {
        "question" : "This is question 27",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 27",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 27",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 27",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 27",
        }
    },
    "question28": {
        "question" : "This is question 28",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 28",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 28",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 28",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 28",
        }
    },
    "question29": {
        "question" : "This is question 29",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 29",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 29",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 29",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 29",
        }
    },
    "question30": {
        "question" : "This is question 30",
        "answers": {
            "correct": "This is correct answer for question 30",
            "incorrect1": "This is incorrect answer 1 for question 30",
            "incorrect2": "This is incorrect answer 2 for question 30",
            "incorrect3": "This is incorrect answer 3 for question 30",
        }
    },
}